Guide to the Lucy Maynard Salmon Papers, 1818-1992 (bulk 1854-1933)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE — INCOMING
  - Correspondence from Others
    - Gragg, Florence Alden, 17 Apr 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - Greenburg, Alex, 5 July 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - Griffith, A. Jeannette, 1915, 1917; (2 letters) (Folder 24.4)
    - Griggs, Anne Seymour, 13 Aug 1917; (1 card) (Folder 47.19)
    - Grover, Clara V., 1889; (2 letters) (Folder 24.4)
    - Hadley, Arthur Twining, 1891-1892; (2 letters) (Folder 47.20)
    - Hadley, Sarah S., 10 May 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Halden, W. S., 15 June 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 24.5)
    - Hall, Edith Rockwell, 1924; (2 letters) (Folder 47.20)
    - Hamlin, Sarah D., 1887-1889; (4 letters) (Folder 24.5)
    - Hannum, Louise M., 7 Feb 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Hanus, Paul H., 1888, 1895-1896; (5 letters) (Folder 24.5)
    - Harding, S. B., 6 Mar 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Harding, Warren [written by presidential secretary], 18 Feb 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Harper, William Rainey, 20 Mar 1891; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Extract of a letter received from a German girl…., Apr 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Hassall, Arthur, 1898, undated; (2 letters) (Folder 47.20)
    - Hastings, Helen M., 14 Apr 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Hatfield, Frederica Davis, [13 Jan 1925]; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Head, Anna, 15 Aug 1907; (1 letter) (Folder 24.5)
    - Heaton, John L. [editor, The (NY) World ], 27 Dec 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Henderson, C. R., 12 Dec 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Hill, Mabel, 7 Oct 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Hofer, Amalie, 24 Nov 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 24.6)
    - Hofer, Ernst, 1882, 1886, 1895-1896, 1921; (5 letters, 1 telegram) (Folder 24.6)
    - Hofer, Marie Fuef, 1913, 1927; (2 letters) (Folder 24.6)
    - Hofernbe, J. W., 17 Nov 1884; (1 letter) (Folder 24.6)
    - Holt, Henry, 1914, 1916; (11 letters, 1 card) (Folder 47.20)
    - Hopkins, Sam M., 1900; (2 letters) (Folder 24.6)
    - Hornblower, William B., 10 Dec 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Hough, Williston S., 1898-1901 undated; (11 letters) (Folder 47.20)
    - Houghton Mifflin Co., 1905-1906; (4 letters) (Folder 24.6)
    - Hubbard, Giles Gray, 1923-1924; (2 letters) (Folder 24.6)
    - Hubbard, M., 9 June 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 24.7)
    - Hubbard, S. F., 22 Sep 1890; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Huddilston, J.H., 7 Oct 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - Hull, Charles H., 6 Feb 1918; (1 letter) (Folder 24.7)
    - Hull, Charles H. to Henry Noble MacCracken, 6 Feb 1918; (1 letter) (Folder 24.7)
    - Hull, Eliza Darling, 12 June 1887; (1 letter) (Folder 24.7)
    - Hull, Lawrence, 1888-1901; (17 letters) (Folder 21.10)
    - Hume, Harrison, 14 Feb 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 24.7)
    - Hunt, Charles W., 1 Apr 1914; (1 letter) (Folder 24.7)
    - Hurlbutt, Mary E., 1916; (5 letters) (Folder 24.7)
    - Hutchins, H. B., 23 Oct 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 47.20)
    - H. M. F., 23 Mar 1870; (1 letter) (Folder 24.7)
    - Ind, W.D., 14 Dec 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 24.8)
    - Irwin, Will, 1 Jan 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Isley, [James] K., 8 Aug, 1887; (1 letter) (Folder 24.8)
    - Jackson, Gertrude, 9 Aug [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Jenkins, Elizabeth R., 9 Aug 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 24.8)
    - Jenkins, Helen D., 17 Jan 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 24.8)
    - Jobe, Mary L., 23 Nov 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Johnson, Helen Louise [General Federation of Women’s Clubs], 1916; (2 letters) (Folder 47.21)
    - Johnson, Woodbridge, 30 May 1904; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Johnstone, Hilda, 12 June 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Judson, Harry Pratt, 23 Feb 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Justice, Anna, 9 Nov 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 24.8)
    - Justice, Henry (with 3 poems), 1907-1917; (7 letters) (Folder 21.11)
    - Justice, Josephine B., 9 Mar 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 24.8)
    - Kate, 1881-1882; (3 letters) (Folder 24.9)
    - Kellogg, A.W., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Kellogg, Louise Phelps [The State Historical Society of Wisconsin], 5 Apr 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Kelso, Tessa, 27 Oct 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Kemp, Ellwood W., 1891, 1900, 1902; (3 letters) (Folder 24.9)
    - Kendall, E., undated; (2 letters) (Folder 47.21)
    - Kimball, Lillian G., 1 Jan 1894; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Kinley, Davis, 8 Mar 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Kinne, Mrs. E.J., 8 Jan 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 24.9)
    - Knauss, James O., 1 Oct 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Knowlton, Daniel C., 1917, 1922; (2 letters) (Folder 47.21)
    - Koch, Theodore Wesley, 1917; (2 letters) (Folder 47.21)
    - Kruell, G., 1890; (2 letters) (Folder 47.21)
    - Laing, Mary E., 1902; (2 letters) (Folder 24.9)
    - Lance, Emma, 12 Feb 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Lance, N. J., 7 Sep 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Larrabee, Don M., 31 Jan 1925; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Larrabee, Rachel, 1881-1897; (13 letters) (Folder 21.12)
    - Larrabee, Rachel, 1899-1927; (29 letters, 1 enclosure) (Folders 22.1 - 22.2)
    - Lasher, Mrs. H.D., [1889]; (2 letters) (Folder 24.9)
    - Lathrop, Adele, 1903-1905, undated; (6 letters) (Folder 22.3)
    - Lathrop, Ella M., 1871-1874; (7 letters) (Folder 22.4)
    - Lathrop, Julia, 15 Apr [no year]; (1 letter, 1 transcript) (Folder 47.21)
    - Lawrence, George A., 1919; (2 letters) (Folder 47.21)
    - [Learned?], J. [G.?], 16 May 1891; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Leonard, Herbert Edwin, 1906, 1915; (2 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Lewis, S. B.D., 24 Mar 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 24.9)
    - The Library Journal, 25 June 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Linchards, Laura L., 6 Nov 1925; (1 letter) (Folder 24.9)
    - Little, C.C., 28 May 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 24.9)
    - Long, Percy W., 12 Aug 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Lord, Chester S., 1919, 1922; (2 letters) (Folder 24.9)
    - Loveman, Amy, 17 July 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 47.21)
    - Lydenhey, H.M., 1922; (2 letters) (Folder 47.21)
    - Lyman, Charles E., 1919, 1922, undated; (4 letters) (Folder 47.21)
    - Lyman, Chester, 21 May 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 24.9)
    - Lyttle, Eugene W., 1902, 1904; (3 letters) (Folder 24.9)
    - Mace, William H., 23 June 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 24.10)
    - MacLeish, Martha Hillard, 17 Nov 1890; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - The Macmillan Company, 1899, 1901; (5 letters) (Folder 47.22)
    - MacMullen, John, 8 Oct 1894; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Mapel, John J., 1883-1889, 1898; (5 letters) (Folder 24.10)
    - Marin, Faith, 6 June 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Mary, Rose and Bertha, 24 June 1881; (1 letter) (Folder 24.10)
    - Mason, Gertrude H., 1875-1908; (31 letters, 1 correspondence card) (Folders 22.6 - 22.7)
    - Mason, William S., 1922-1923; (3 letters) (Folder 47.22)
    - McAndrew, W.A., 30 Oct 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 24.10)
    - McAndrews, W., 8 Feb 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - McCrea, Jamie, 5 Jan 1871; (1 letter) (Folder 24.10)
    - McDonald, James H., 21 Dec 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 24.10)
    - McGregor High School, [23 May 1881?] and 15 June 1881; (2 letters) (Folder 24.10)
    - McLaughlin, Andrew C., 20 Feb 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 24.10)
    - McMillay, Jessie M., 2 Dec 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 24.10)
    - McMurry, Charles A. (with 1 invitation list), 1901-1903; (9 letters) (Folder 22.5)
    - McNitt, Esther U., 1915; (2 letters) (Folder 47.22)
    - Mead, Edwin D., 1890, 1894; (2 letters) (Folder 47.22)
    - Meriwether, C., 16 Apr 1894; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Merkle, John, 21 June 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 24.10)
    - Merritt, Anne P., 25 Nov 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Merritt, Edwin A., Jr., 7 Apr 1909; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Merritt, Jesse F., 2 Aug [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 24.11)
    - Meyer, Anne Latham, 28 Dec 1918; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Michigan, University of, 10 Feb 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Michigan Historical Commission, 7 Dec 1918; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Miller, Walter, 1888-1889; (6 letters) (Folder 24.11)
    - Million, Helen Lovell, 2 Dec 1899; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Moffitt, Rebecca A., 1886; (2 letters) (Folder 24.11)
    - Monroe, Paul, 4 May 1911; (1 letter) (Folder 24.11)
    - Monti, Luigi, 4 Aug 1885; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Moore, Charles, 1919-1921; (2 letters) (Folder 47.22)
    - Moore, Nancy M., 22 Feb [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 24.11)
    - Morgenthau, Henry, 1921; (2 letters) (Folder 47.22)
    - Morris, Victoria H., [circa 1887]; (1 letter) (Folder 24.11)
    - Morschaush, Joseph, 8 Feb 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Murphy, Claudia Quigley, 20 July 1891; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Myers, Irene, T., 19 Nov 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 47.22)
    - Neilson, Nellie, 1918-1922, undated; (10 letters) (Folder 47.23)
    - Nettleton, George H., 1922-1923; (4 letters) (Folder 47.23)
    - Nettleton, Walter, 15 Nov [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 47.23)
    - Nevin, R. J., 10 May [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 47.23)
    - The New Century Club, 1911-1912; (2 letters) (Folder 47.23)
    - The New York Evening Post, 1921, 1923 undated; (4 letters) (Folder 47.23)
    - Nichols, A. R., 24 Aug 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.23)
    - Nicholls, Blanche G., 24 July 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 24.12)
    - Nock, Albert Jay, 1920, 1922; (2 letters) (Folder 47.23)
    - Nellegar, Don A., 1918; (2 letters) (Folder 47.23)
    - Nolen, John, 1909-1910, 1920; (5 letters) (Folder 47.23)
    - Nolland, Albert P., undated; (1 card) (Folder 24.12)
    - Nolton, A. H., 27 Feb 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 24.12)
    - North, Mrs. C.C., 1867; (1 letter) (Folder 24.12)
    - Norrie, Margaret, 7 Feb 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.23)
    - The North American Review, 1916; (2 letters) (Folder 47.23)
    - Norton-Woods, M. E., 1894, 1896; (4 letters) (Folder 47.23)
    - Nourse, Annie C.S., 1916-1917; (3 letters) (Folder 24.12)
    - O’Connor, Charles A., 15 Apr 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 24.12)
    - O’Leary, H.A., 1923; (2 letters) (Folder 47.23)
    - O’Neill, Lawrence, 12 Feb 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 47.23)
    - Orvis, Susan A., 1900-1901; (2 letters) (Folder 24.12)
    - Osborn, Albert D., 1926; (2 letters) (Folder 24.12)
    - Oswald, Garrison Villard, 1916-1922; (7 letters) (Folder 22.8)
    - The Outlook, 27 Feb 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 47.23)
    - Page, Walter H., 6 Dec 1907; (1 letter) (Folder 24.13)
    - Palmer, Alice Freeman and several letters to Mrs. Palmer from others, 1885- 1890, undated; (11 letters) (Folder 47.23)
    - Palmer, T. W., 10 April 1888; (1 letter) (Folder 24.13)
    - Park, Marion, 2 Feb 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.24)
    - Parsons, W. W., 1888; (2 letters) (Folder 24.13)
    - Pattison, T. Hammond, 19 Apr 1897; (1 card) (Folder 47.24)
    - Payne, William H., 1 Dec 1890; (1 letter) (Folder 47.24)
    - Peet, Hubert W., 19 Feb 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 24.13)
    - Pendleton, Ellen Fitz, 1923; (2 letters) (Folder 47.24)
    - Pendleton, E. W., 6 July 1887; (1 letter) (Folder 24.13)
    - Pennell, Elizabeth Robins, 17 Apr 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 24.13)
    - Perkins, L., 7 Jan 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 47.24)
    - Perkins, L. S. W, 1902-1905; (7 letters, 2 postcards) (Folder 22.9)
    - Perry, Bliss, 1900-1908, [1910?]; (9 letters) (Folder 24.13)
    - Perry, Jeannette B., 21 Sep 1893; (1 letter, 1 transcript) (Folder 24.13)
    - Pettit, G. A., 24 Feb 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 47.23)
    - Petrie, F., 19 June 1888; (1 letter) (Folder 25.1)
    - Pettergill, Lillian, 16 Jan 1903; (1 letter) (Folder 25.1)
    - Pick, Robert F. [bookseller], 1917-1920 (Folders 47.31 - 47.33)
    - Pidgin, Charles F., 2 Mar 1890; (1 letter) (Folder 47.24)
    - Pierce, E.C., 1886-1897, undated; (6 letters) (Folder 25.1)
    - Platt, Edmund, 1916, 1919; (2 letters) (Folder 47.24)
    - Platt, Howard, 1910; (2 letters) (Folder 47.24)
    - Pond, Horace, 1924; (3 letters) (Folder 25.1)
    - Poole, William F., 10 Apr 1893; (1 letter) (Folder 47.24)
    - Poughkeepsie, Mayor of, 12 May 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 47.24)
    - President and Regents of the University of Michigan, [1926]; (1 card) (Folder 25.1)
    - Prudden, Adah J., 10 Feb 1907; (1 letter) (Folder 47.24)
    - Purdue, A.H., 1900; (2 letters) (Folder 47.24)
    - Putnam, Bertha, 29 Nov 1909; (1 letter) (Folder 47.24)
    - Putnam, Ruth, 1900-1926, undated; (38 letters, 2 clippings, 1 card) (Folder 47.25)
    - Quigley, Margery, 20 July 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 25.2)
    - Ratcliffe, S. K., 11 Nov [no year]; (1 card) (Folder 47.26)
    - Redhead, E.R., 20 May 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 25.2)
    - Reen, Charles, 28 Nov 1920; (1 letter) (Folder 25.2)
    - Rembaugh, T. S., 15 May 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 47.26)
    - Remy, Charles Mason, 6 Apr 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 47.26)
    - Reynolds, Helen W., 1921; (2 letters) (Folder 47.26)
    - Rhoads, James E., 1886-1887; (2 letters) (Folder 25.2)
    - Rice, Charles L., 1916, 1922; (2 letters) (Folder 25.2)
    - Richardson, E. C., 18 Dec 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 47.26)
    - Richmond, Mary E., 1915-1917; (6 letters) (Folder 47.26)
    - Rigby, Irving, 1923; (11 letters) (Folder 22.10)
    - Ripley, Joseph, 20 Nov 1888; (1 letter) (Folder 25.2)
    - Ripper, Julie S., 1 May 1867; (1 letter) (Folder 25.2)
    - Robbins, Frank Egleston, 1926; (3 letters) (Folder 25.2)
    - Robinson, Chalfant, [1902?], 1902, 1923-1926; (7 letters) (Folder 25.2)
    - Robinson, Winifred, 1922; (2 letters) (Folder 47.26)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 1893; (2 letters) (Folder 22.11)
    - Rorison, Clair and Arda Bates, 24 May 1920; (1 letter) (Folder 25.2)
    - Ryan, Dixon, 20 Jan 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 47.26)
    - Sanders, Frank K., 27 Jan 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.26)
    - Sanders, Henry M., 25 June [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 47.26)
    - Sands, Beatrice, 15 July 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.26)
    - Sanford, Mabel Warren, 21 Nov 1894; (1 letter) (Folder 47.26)
    - Satterthwaite, Sarah E., 1887-1924; (5 letters, 2 postcards) (Folder 22.12)
    - Schneider, E.E., undated; (1 pamphlet) (Folder 47.26)
    - Schneider, Marie S., 3 Aug 1899; (1 letter) (Folder 47.26)
    - Scott, Austin, 1891, 1894-1895; (4 letters) (Folder 47.26)
    - Scott, Harriet M., 22 Jan 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Scranton, Henriette, 1926; (2 letters) (Folder 25.3)
    - Sebring, Emma G., 7 June 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Sedgwick, Ellen [The Atlantic Monthly], 1916; (2 letters) (Folder 47.27)
    - Sells Ltd, 8 May 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Sewall, Mary Wright, 19 Feb 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Shaw, Albert [The Review of Reviews], 1895-1896; (6 letters) (Folder 47.27)
    - Shaw, Winifred B., 16 June 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 25.3)
    - Shepard, W.J., 4 Mar 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 25.3)
    - Shively, George, 1921-1922; (2 letters) (Folder 47.27)
    - Smith, Carman N., 1887-1888; (3 letters) (Folder 25.3)
    - Smith, Charles Foster, 17 Feb 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Smith, Elisa M., 23 Oct 1887; (1 letter) (Folder 25.3)
    - Smith, Erwin F., 18 July 1888; (1 letter) (Folder 25.3)
    - Smith, Howard B., 1889; (2 letters) (Folder 25.3)
    - Smith, Mary Roberts, 1893-1901; (3 letters) (Folder 47.27)
    - Smith, William W., 1907; (1 letter) (Folder 22.13)
    - Soomis, Ruth, 2 Apr [1903]; (1 letter) (Folder 25.3)
    - Sotheran, Henry & Co., 2 Oct 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Southworth, Effir A., 10 June 1887; (1 letter) (Folder 25.4)
    - Spalding, V.M., 1887-1889; (9 letters) (Folder 22.14)
    - Spencer, Truman J., 11 June 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Spender, A. E., 29 July 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Squires, W.H., 16 May 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 25.4)
    - Stanley, L. E., 18 Nov 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 25.4)
    - Stead, William, Jr., 1900-1905; (6 letters) (Folder 47.27)
    - Steere, J. H., 20 Sep 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 25.4)
    - Stead, William, Jr. (Folder 47.27)
    - Stevenson, H.A., 16 Apr 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 25.4)
    - Stewart, A. A., 1887-1923; (7 letters) (Folder 23.1)
    - Stimson, Henry A., 1916-1922; (2 letters, 1 card) (Folder 47.27)
    - Story, Helen E., 22 Oct [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Stowell, Amelia E., 11 Mar 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Strong, Augustus, 10 Jan 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Strong, Kate, 21 Jan 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 47.27)
    - Strunk, William E. Jr. and one to Strunk from LMS, 1899-1908, 1921-1925; (20 letters) (Folder 47.28)
    - Sullivan, James, 15 Oct 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 47.28)
    - Sutro, Adolph, 3 Mar 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 47.28)
    - Sutton, M. A. O., 14 Nov 1888; (1 letter, 1 transcript) (Folder 25.4)
    - Swan, Frances W., 1 Jan 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 47.28)
    - Swann, Arthur, 2 June 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.28)
    - Taylor, G. Winifred, 19 Sep 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 47.29)
    - Taylor, Kate H., 1890-1891; (2 cards, 1 letter) (Folder 25.5)
    - Taylor, Robert E., 1892-1896; (3 letters) (Folder 47.29)
    - Thacher, Emma Treadwell, 18 Feb 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 25.5)
    - Thacher, John Boyd, 5 Nov 1905; (1 letter) (Folder 25.5)
    - Thallon, Grace L., 28 May 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 25.5)
    - Thallon, Ida to her mother, 12 May 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 25.5)
    - Thomas, Calvin, 1889; (15 letters) (Folder 23.2)
    - Thomas, M. Carey, 10 Sep 1912; (1 letter) (Folder 25.5)
    - Thorpe, Frances H., 2 Dec 1890; (1 letter) (Folder 47.29)
    - Tremain, Mary, 1887-1924, undated; (18 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 23.3)
    - Trent, W. P., 17 Sep 1908; (1 letter) (Folder 47.29)
    - Turnbull, George S., 1925; (2 letters) (Folder 25.5)
    - Underhill, Charles M., 1922; (2 letters) (Folder 25.6)
    - Updegraff, Theodore, 1894-1895; (3 letters) (Folder 47.29)
    - Vaught, U. A., 3 Sep 1910; (1 letter) (Folder 25.6)
    - Villard, Fanny Garrison, 1921, 1923; (2 letters) (Folder 47.29)
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison and one letter to Villard from LMS, 1917-1926, undated; (5 letters) (Folder 47.29)
    - Vrooman, A. B., 24 July 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.29)
    - Vrooman, Walter, 22 Jan 1899; (1 letter) (Folder 47.29)
    - Wagner, Mary Swain, 31 Aug 1918; (1 letter) (Folder 47.29)
    - Waite, B.S., 18 Sep 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 25.6)
    - Walker, Leslie, 19 July 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 47.29)
    - Walker, Marie Louise, 16 June 1887; (1 letter) (Folder 25.6)
    - Wall, Alexander J., 1922; (2 letters) (Folder 47.29)
    - Walsh, Thomas J., 12 Feb 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 25.6)
    - Letter to Thomas J. Walsh from special assistant to the attorney general for war work, 10 Feb 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 25.6)
    - Walter, Anne, 28 Jan 1881; (1 letter) (Folder 25.6)
    - Walton, Perry, 1922-1924; (12 letters) (Folder 47.29)
    - Ward, Estelle Frances, 12 June 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.30)
    - Ward, George A., 7 Apr 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 25.6)
    - Ware, B., 28 Dec 1905; (1 letter) (Folder 25.6)
    - Warren, Henry P., 6 Mar 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 25.6)
    - Washburn, Mario Foster, 26 Jan 1904; (1 letter) (Folder 25.6)
    - Webb, Griswold, 23 Sep 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 47.30)
    - Wells, Florence, 1921, undated; (3 letters) (Folder 47.30)
    - Whaley, Reverend and Mrs. Samuel (friends of Lucy Maynard Salmon's parents from Riverhead, NY — includes a copy of an 1893 printed sermon, "Fifty Years in the Ministry"), 1886-1907 (Folders 46.7 - 46.13)
    - Whaley, Sophia D., [circa 1860], 1864, 1889; (5 letters) (Folder 25.7)
    - Wigmore, John H., 2 Apr 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 47.30)
    - Williams, Alice, 1901, 1905, 1906, 1923-1924; (6 letters, 1 transcript) (Folder 25.7)
    - Williams J. B. (Joseph George Muddiman), 23 Jan 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 47.30)
    - Williams, [?], 16 Feb 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 47.30)
    - Woodbury, William L., 7 Feb 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 25.7)
    - Woods, W. B., 1897, 1921; (3 letters) (Folder 47.30)
    - Worde, M. E. Sooton, 30 Mar 1887; (1 letter) (Folder 25.7)
    - Wright, Carroll D., 11 Mar 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 47.30)
    - Wroth, Lawrence C., 31 Mar 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.30)
    - Yale University Press, 1919; (2 letters) (Folder 47.30)
    - Young, Henry L., 1895, 1898; (2 letters) (Folder 25.7)
    - Young, Robert J., 1924-1925; (2 letters) (Folder 25.7)
    - Yuan, T.L., 23 June 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.30)
    - Zimmern, Alice, 1919, undated; (5 letters) (Folder 47.30)
    - Envelopes to and from LMS, 1886-1926; (8 envelopes) (Folder 25.8)
    - Unidentified letters and statement, 1891, 1909, undated; (4 letters, 2 cards) (Folder 47.30)
- SERIES III. CORRESPONDENCE — To and From Others
  - Correspondence to Adelaide Underhill
    - Barnum, Clara L., 15 Jan 1932; (1 letter) (Folder 29.6)
    - Bothwood, Elvina W., 20 May 1935; (1 letter) (Folder 29.6)
    - Burt, Lelia W., 17 Mar 1933; (1 letter) (Folder 29.6)
    - Cole, Helen C., 6 Nov 1933; (1 letter) (Folder 29.6)
    - Daniels Keck, Anna, 1928; (2 letters) (Folder 29.6)
    - Davenport, Charles B., 1 Jan 1936; (1 letter) (Folder 29.6)
    - Davenport, W.E., 1928, 1935, 1936; (3 letters) (Folder 29.6)
    - Eidlitz, Dorothy Meigs, 7 Apr 1936; (1 letter) (Folder 29.6)
    - Ellery, Eloise, 1933; (2 letters) (Folder 29.6)
    - Gaviller, Barbara, 22 Oct 1935; (1 letter) (Folder 29.6)
    - Hatcher, O. Latham, [1927]; (1 card) (Folder 29.6)
    - Jameson, J. Franklin, 1936; (2 letters) (Folder 24.8)
    - Kendig, M. Mercer, 17 Aug 1935; (1 letter) (Folder 29.6)
    - Larrabee, Rachel, 1927-1928, 1932, 1934-1935; (7 letters) (Folder 29.7)
    - McCrosky, Josephine, 3 Jan 1936; (1 letter) (Folder 29.7)
    - Mineah, Anna, 3 Aug 1935; (1 letter) (Folder 29.7)
    - Moore, Anne, 11 Dec 1935; (1 letter) (Folder 29.7)
    - Randolph, Lucile, with a letter from Louise Fargo Brown to Randolph, 1927-1943 (Folder 46.39)
    - Rickert, Edith, 17 Dec 1935; (1 letter) (Folder 29.7)
    - Salmon, Maynard Hubbard, 1933, 1935; (4 letters) (Folder 29.7)
    - Satterthwaite, Sarah E., 1936; (1 letter, 1 card) (Folder 29.8)
    - Sewall, Kate Strong, 14 Mar 1927; ( 1 letter) (Folder 29.8)
    - Sinsabaugh, Henrietta, 28 Sep 1935; (1 letter) (Folder 29.8)
    - Strong, Eliza M., 20 Jan 1936; (1 letter) (Folder 29.8)
    - Taylor, James Monroe, 1907; (2 letters) (Folder 29.8)
    - Taylor, Lilly Ross, 6 Mar 1927; (1 letter) (Folder 29.8)
    - Updegraff, Elizabeth, Apr 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 29.8)
    - Whaley, Mrs., 1903-1907 (Folders 46.17 - 46.18)
    - Williams, Ida, 4 Jan 1936; (1 letter) (Folder 29.8)
    - Zen, Sophia Chen, 11 Apr 1936; (1 letter) (Folder 29.8)
  - Correspondence from Adelaide Underhill to Others
    - Borden, Fanny, 1927, 1932, 1935; (2 letters, 1 card) (Folder 29.10)
    - Brown, Louise Fargo, 21 Jan 1935; (1 letter) (Folder 29.10)
    - Cutler, [Amelia Macdonald?] (VC 1904), 1929-1930; (2 letters) (Folder 29.10)
    - Fraser, Minnie, 1913-1926, 1927 (Folder 46.40)
    - Taylor, James Monroe, [Feb 1907]; (1 letter) (Folder 29.10)
    - Whaley, Mrs. (Folder 46.16)
  - Others to Others
    - Bishop, William Warner to Miss Borden, 11 Oct 1935; (1 letter) (Folder 28.9)
    - Brusie, Charles Frederick to James Monroe Taylor, 25 Sep 1905; (1 letter) (Folder 28.9)
    - Bryan, E.B. to Cornelia M. Raymond, 9 July 1927; (1 letter) (Folder 28.9)
    - Aunt Clara to Calvin, 7 Nov 1855; (1 letter) (Folder 28.9)
    - Crowell, Phebe P. to Aunt, 4 Nov 1873; (1 letter) (Folder 28.9)
    - Durant, D. to Curriculum Committee, [1917]; (1 letter) (Folder 28.9)
    - Dryerid, H.L. to Frank Hiscock, 25 Jan 1887; (1 letter) (Folder 28.9)
    - Eaton, Artemus to Mr. Maynard, 22 July 1843; (1 letter) (Folder 28.9)